Hey,
blue.
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
H.
Wait, I forgot to uh Yeah, bye. Hello
everyone.
Mortal.
Where is my model?
Oh my god.
M
refresh. Okay, I'm here. Hello.
Hi.
So, um
what the
uh I have to change my mic
apparently.
Okay. Hello.
Okay. Hi. Hi.
Uh
uh uh yeah. Uh oh my god, I struggle
struggle.
But yeah, today we'll be doing uh
reading and some grammar stuff. Okay,
I have classes by
uh 12 or 1 p.m.
Uh so we will do this for 2 hours.
Okay.
And I
hi.
Hello.
Good morning.
Hello. Hello.
Uh,
man, I'm so unprepared.
I'm so unprepared.
Discord
X.
I forgot to tweet that I'm live on
I'm live on Twitter. I mean X. Call it X
now.
Hi.
Uh
Twitter, right? Hi XL SL X. Yeah. Uh
Tweet Twitter.
ground.
I feel like I'm not supposed to use the
background.
No commission.
Commission. Uh
uh commission um
um picture
mate I for wait how do you say
pictureground
pix
I just
the beautiful sky, the night sky. It's
really nice, right?
It's really really nice. So
hi. Uh
so
uh steadies right
I will share my screen
bro. Yeah I'll have to do that. Yeah.
Uh why is my discord not
uh announcement not being made?
something.
There was one more comment.
Hi.
Yes.
Uh
so I have some ideas on how to proceed
today.
Okay.
Yesterday I found a news website I could
use
uh
nk
website.
Oh my god, my grammar is so bad.
So yeah, I found a NHK website called
NHK
uh news web easy.
So so I can read news.
Yeah, world news.
Uh, and it has easy Japanese.
So,
Benji Benina
like
one second. Um,
couldn't
wait. Why is it not announcing that I'm
live?
Hello, obnoxious. Good morning.
Okay, give me a minute.
No live streams found.
I'm live though.
Okay, one second. I'll just fix the live
stream. Okay,
I already wasted uh 10 minutes. Yeah,
bye.
This is bad. Oh my god, this is bad.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Twitter.
Uh
short stream.
Short steady stream.
Uh not there.
Ah.
Yeah, that's fine.
Have you ever considered streaming with
Yosha Foger? Uh I I did collabs with her
in the past.
I uh did collabs with her in the past.
We had a collab. It's in my channel. Uh
we both streamed together. We played
this game called um
I forgot the name. It was like a really
fun game.
Uh yeah. Yeah.
Hello MC obvious welcome. Good morning.
Uh
give me a minute people. I I'll just do
something real quick. I'm sorry. I
supposed
uh I'm supposed to start early but
stuff not working whenever I wish to
stream.
Uh
uh
come on come on come on
schedule. Okay.
I just realized you're not using your
original model.
Uh, you mean the live duty?
I stopped using that. I won't use it
anymore.
Uh, I have a new one coming.
Uh, due to stuff I'm not uh wanting to
like go back to my older models.
Uh, yeah.
kind of got PTSD with it for for now.
But um I mean I can still use it if I
wish to, but I'm making myself not do
it. It is fine. Whatever I have right
now, I'm I'm happy with it. The PNG, I
do have a newer model,
uh new new jocknik model. Uh it's not
rig rigged yet. Uh so I probably will be
releasing that to the public by this
year probably around somewhere this
year. Uh but that will be starting as
PNG though cuz uh again rigging is
expensive. No I am broke.
Uh yeah.
So uh even if I'm looking like this, I
hope you will consider me.
Anyway,
um she's vegetarian. You I'm I eat both
nonveg and veg.
I
trying something out.
You can say that. Yep.
M why is everything breaking?
Uh
I'm way but I do uh but I do next time
meditate house.
Ah so you like Indiana. That's nice.
That's nice.
You should come by to India, I guess.
Like try out food. There's like a lot of
food items here.
The spices and everything.
Yeah.
Live stream detected. Okay. G announcing
ID. Creating new announcement
stream updated. Completed streams and
finalized. Okay. Okay. Now with this the
announcement. Okay. Finally. Okay. Hi.
Uh I'll switch to the screen. Uh we'll
start with it. I know I am 18 19 minutes
late. I'm so sorry.
I'm not sure if I'll get banned today uh
because I'm uh
showing a PDF
uh textbook.
Uh but we'll start with Oh, yeah. Yeah.
We'll we'll do this actually.
Elementary
textbook.
Yeah, we'll do this. Hi
Wait, wait. I should not show the front
cover. I might get in trouble. Hello.
Uh, good evening. No, no. Good morning.
Sorry.
Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Good morning.
Uh, hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Um,
uh,
okay. So we'll mainly do some reading
practice actually. Uh also the NHSK
website I was talking about. Uh there's
two websites actually. Uh NHK.
So this is the website I found
yesterday. I was like thinking can I
like read newspapers or something? Uh
can I like read newspapers or something
which is easy to read? So like there's
like news stuff here.
It'll be like easier for me to like
read. They have a toggle. Where's the
toggle? Wait, they had a toggle though.
Wait, they had a toggle though. Wait,
where is it?
They had a toggle though. Uh, wait.
The another site is called Asahi.
Asai.
Uh
wait, is it this one? No, wait.
As a
h Yasashi. Yeah. Yeah. Yasashi. Got it.
This one uh this one has a toggle for
furigana. If if a kanji I don't know, I
can read it. Uh read it from the top.
I'll write it. write the kanji down so I
can learn it so I don't forget it.
Uh and um there then there's like easy
way as well.
Uh
waka.
Yeah. Yeah. Easy to understand uh
thingy. I feel like this is just
spacing.
Yeah. So there's like audio version as
well and some normal written version as
well. Hello Solar. Welcome.
Good morning.
Indeed looks easy Japanese. So so yes.
Oh hi.
Uh hi. So we'll we'll try that. Okay.
Um,
I'll just make a new window and put it
here.
Okay, I'll just uh
Oh, wait. You can see my whole screen.
Oh, it's not Oh, it's not the whole brow
Oh my god, I forgot.
Hold up. Uh,
hold up. Hold up. Not there.
Okay, there you go. That should be good.
Let me close the background items.
I was also going through the kanis
and yeah, I found a good website by the
way. It's called Kanji Kana. So I can
like select N4 and like click on one of
the kanis and it gives me the stroke
order like this a visualization is there
so I don't forget the correct stroke
patterns and also they give the kunomi
and onomi stuff and the radicals which
are used for this kanji and they have
common words. This is this is good for
me cuz I keep forgetting like okay this
kanji I've seen it somewhere but how do
I read it when it's together with
another kanji's
yeah really uh really interesting.
Uh
don't ask why I'm here when it's 11:41
p.m. for me. Ah. Oh, yeah. It's late for
you. No,
I keep forgetting that everyone is from
a different uh time zone.
Uh, hi. Um,
one second. Um,
I just want to check my
uh this thing.
Well, it's a steady stream. Uh I won't I
will be talking here and there and also
doing my best to write it down in my
notebook. I won't be doing the thing I
used to do on my stream before for my
previous study streams. I used to use
like um Canva or like a drawing app and
like uh like visually drew it while I
was writing down and stuff, right? Uh
this time I'll just um I'll at this time
I'll just uh write it down in my
notebook notebook. I'll memo it down in
my physical notebook
rather than writing it digitally and uh
wasting time. So
yeah.
Hello M. Good morning. Hello. Hello.
So I got like homework to do if I'm
correct. Um
if I am correct I have to do read. Yeah.
Yeah. We can do do this. Oh yeah. Yeah.
We can do this. Oh yeah, we can do this
actually. Oh, thank you.
Hello Daniela. Good morning. Oh my god,
a lot of people coming by.
Hello. I missed you guys.
Hi there. I'm doing good. I'm doing
great. My exams are on Sunday this
Sunday. So, I'm been uh been uh trying
my hardest to, you know, study. I have
to study. If I fail, I'm dead. I can't
fail. I must not fail.
I failed once. I cannot fail twice.
Hi. Uh dialogue. Let's uh do some Kaiba
reading. Okay. Hi. I like uh full screen
this so it's easier for to read. Hi
uh
deno
and then we got
yeah
owner uh not
okay then John. Okay. John and Deno.
Okay. Hi. Next.
Hi.
Uh,
retia.
Little
John. What?
What?
This is right.
Okay. John,
you stream on OBS or Streamlabs? Who
uses Streamlabs in 2026?
I uh for interrupting while I was
reading I use uh
I use Mel Studio as you can see Mel
Studio. It's laggy. But yeah, I use Mel
and my 24x7 channel runs OBS, which is
currently live. But yeah, to um I switch
I I use both OBS and uh Mel
Yeah, Mel Studio and OBS. Hi.
coming back.
John,
wait.
Ah, wait. Why doesn't it show up?
Wait. Why is it not showing it up?
Okay.
Uh, let me
look it up. Wait, I can't look it up.
Wait, what?
Wait, I can't look the kanji up. Oh,
okay. M.
Uh, this is
Boou.
Wait,
she and you. Shu.
No.
Coco.
Oh.
this one.
Yeah, I believe this is like a part-time
recruitment uh poster.
Something like that. Oh my god, my my my
my my my PC dying.
Yeah, but
I'm busy dying. I mean,
uh, hi
Are you buy
me this?
That's so good. That's
Wait, how? Wait, can I use or
uh
to meet I know this KJ I studed it
yesterday. Uh
hash
can you come to the store today? Uh yeah
store today.
Can I
Wait,
wait.
Oh my god. What's happening? I need to
practice, bro. Oh my god. And this is
bad.
This is bad. Bad.
Yeah. Bye. This is bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
Uh.
No.
Oh my god. Uh.
This is bad bad bad bad. Uh
okay. Uh John.
Okay. Let's read it again. Okay. I have
to read it again.
Hi
Uh,
somebody must
That's
Mr.
She must die.
Okay. So in translation it's like uh
owner of the restaurant.
Hi uh
uh hi uh this is uh little Asia.
Uh John the guy who's calling. Uh hello
uh uh hello. My name is John.
Uh
but I saw a part-time po uh part-time
recruitment poster.
Uh I saw a part-time recruitment poster.
Uh
poster and uh the restaurant owner is
like, "Oh, I see. So, uh let's meet and
talk. Can you come to the store today?
Can you come to the Can you get to the
store?
uh like restaurant and John is like
uh today I can't
but if it's tomorrow I be I I will be I
might be able to I will be able to make
it tomorrow. Yeah. And uh the restaurant
also says I I understand
uh so you can't come today.
Uh so
let's uh
uh to uh tomorrow at like 1
Wait, wait.
1 hour, right?
Oh, 1. Wait, 1 a.m.
Hello, Ia.
Good morning. It's uh it is Yeah. Uh
tomorrow at 1:00 a.m. or 100 p.m. Uh can
you make it? Then John is like, "Uh, oh,
1 hour." Yeah. Uh, it right. 1:00 a.m.
over that timing. Yeah, I got it. Short
conversation. Hi. Now part two.
Now comes part two.
One second.
Let me just There was this error
message.
Hi. At the restaurant. So, both John and
the owner are in the restaurant and they
are going to talk.
I
That's
Oh, I see what they did. Uh, they did
the grammar to grammar.
Hi. Uh,
Then
Ashara.
Hi
Oh my god, I actually read it well.
Wow, I actually read it well. Oh my god.
Nice.
Oh my god. I have I I have what it takes
to do it. Yeah. Bye.
So,
I actually did it. Okay. Okay. So a
translation uh the two people are in the
restaurant and then Joe uh the owner is
like uh one son is actually John's last
name. So John um
why did you choose uh why did you choose
to
uh like
yeah why did you choose this uh
part-time job why what how do I say this
uh what made you be interested in this
part-time job the owner asked Jaw asks
John and John replies with it's
interesting
and uh you get to meet pe new people.
Uh yeah, you get to meet new people and
also you get to you uh he gets to use
Japanese more.
Yeah. And uh the owner asks uh
have you worked uh in any Japanese
uh like in Japan? Have you worked
anywhere else?
And John responds
with yes I have worked in a convenience
store
uh before as a part-time a part-timer.
Yeah. Then uh then ch the owner asks
again
uh
can you start tomorrow
and John responds yes
let's work together and uh owner says
let's do our best hi
next one we have
professor yamashta comes comes to the
place. Yeah.
So, it's actually uh a customer
and John. This is John. Oh, wait. You
can't see it. Yeah. This is John
and this is the Professor Yamashita
song. Hi. Okay, let's go. Let's read
this. Professor Yamashta come to Hi.
Uh,
watch the sunset.
Uh John
uh
is
m
Wait,
wait, wait, wait. Read it carefully.
Wait.
Okay. He went into the topic. Okay.
Itchy bun. Itchy. Wait. It bun
ninki
nink.
translation uh
uh welcome and oh it's sense
professor Yamashta and Professor
Yamashta says uh John
are you working part-time here
are you doing part time here John yes
I've been doing it for a week, three
times.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Isuka, wait.
Mate, I forgot my date stuff. Uh, is
week, right? I've been doing it for a
week.
Okay. In a week, I do it three times,
right? Yeah. Yeah. So, he does it in a
week, three times.
part-time job here in the restaurant
Little Asia.
And professor was like, "Oh, I see." Um
from the menu uh which which seems uh
what which uh food
or saw which uh which item from the menu
is good cuz why he went into the topic
is because
literally holding the menu over here and
John is like asking sir what you order.
So yeah, and he goes back into the thing
he came here for. So yeah,
and John is like um this um if uh this
curry um
uh curry uh is
really um recommended
like um most recommended
wait ninki is popular. Okay, wait.
Ninkimona famous right? So this curry is
most popular here. Uh
he says that and yamashi
uh that looks tasty.
So let's have I'll have that to eat.
My my translation is bad.
Yeah. Bye. Okay. It's actually 1:00.
Okay. Not one. Um Okay, got it. And this
is the English translation of what we
have read.
Popular word. Yeah, famous popular one
by vocabulary. Time for reading this
adult.
So fto
fji
and hito kanji
photo
um bangoshi
bangi
I I don't know these counties I think I
studied it I forgot how about
I
ko
kimono kimono traditional
mono kji
and key
um
set
sweater
and get Um,
wait. Um,
gaki. Wait. Gi
gaki. Oh. Oh, wait. Gaki and gaki is
different.
Oh yeah.
Oh, wait. I forgot. Oh, yeah.
Gaki is like brat in English, right?
Goki is like bread.
Yeah. Gi.
Yeah.
Gi.
Uh, one second.
Let me check something.
That is my
kick chat. Okay.
Uh gi
what?
Wait.
Oh, it's okay. Okay. Okay. I was like
thinking
I was like, wait, why is there a
like
uh G
G
wait
m
instrument.
Okay. Double K. Double K. Hi. Double K.
elephant
body. This kind is also important. And
uh
Goku
foreign language
language
Bo
boomo. Yeah, boom grammar. Yeah, bu.
I'll just go through this uh quickly and
just um I think I have to go down to
page 50
a
uh man
mansion.
Uh
C
coco
miss
Oh. Uh, coco.
Oh, I It's not poss. Okay. Okay. Coco.
Ah, Coco.
Oh, wait. I have See, I have heard that
word in
like Apex, right? It has that thingy.
Co. Wait, that's announcement. Wait,
mate. This say announcement.
Yeah. Oh, no. My bad.
Bua go koku. Yeah. Thank you.
Go.
Yeah. Yaku. So, promise.
Hi. Uh
uh I like uh
done right.
I could read this but I am running out
of time. Right. Um I could read this but
it's fine. Um
let me double check my WhatsApp. S no
message.
Okay. Uh we will mainly do reading.
Yeah. Yeah. Valentine's Day. Hi. Let's
do this. Valentine.
Hi. A month before Valentine's Day.
May and
uh ui may and u ei
you. Hi.
Hi. Let's go,
Mary.
Valentine.
Uh. Uh. Valentine.
No. Valentine day. No,
that's
Uh oh. Yeah, I have to do translation.
Right. So Mary asks uh on Valentine's
Day,
what what do you what do you think uh I
should
uh what do you think I should give
like something good I should give?
Hello, good morning.
So this and uh UISan is like
yeah
if it's uh like not if it's uh Teshi for
Teshi he uh
uh he
likes to wear
he always likes to wear the same
sweater.
Uh,
so you could
get him a sweater.
You could try getting him a sweater for
Valentine's. Then Mary's like,
that seems like a good idea.
Yeah. Oh my god, I'm bad at translating.
Yeah. Bye.
M.
What do you think is good for Valent?
Ah, that's what he's h Yeah, I'm bad at
translation guys.
Uh, you studying Japanese? Yes. Uh, just
studying. I have an exam on Sunday.
And for um Yeah. And for exam I have to
write
uh I've been I have to like learn
revise everything. and uh learn as if
I have to survive a moment. Yeah, I
cannot fail the second time. So yeah, I
have to learn.
I don't want to be put on N4 class in
Japan. Okay. Like I would love it if
they would put me in N3 class, but if
I'm put in N4, that would mean like I
studied N4 like how many months now?
uh last
all uh October I started this course uh
the N4 lessons right so October November
December January February
March
6 months now it's been 6 months I'm
studying for and I'm like slacking off I
don't want to study and for again for
like next 6 months there I'll be wasting
time I want to direct directly go into
entry. But yeah, I feel like I'm not
ready yet to go to entry because of my
lack of reading skills and kanji stuff
and also the use usage of grammar. My
min grammar usage is bad as well. Yeah,
it's really bad. I have to work hard,
man. Yeah. Bye.
I have to work hard.
anyone.
Uh
let me put this in the side so I can
read my chat. Okay. Hi. Uh second one on
Valentine's Day Mary and Okay. Mary.
Uh
yeah,
wait.
What is wrong with my reading?
Econ
Mary
What?
Okay.
Oh, wait. This is the knitting kanji.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. He's asking if you did
you knitted yourself.
Wait or something. Wait, is it I I I
need a double conf.
How do I
look up in Yan?
Yan do. Oh, are you don't you? Why are
you not coming?
Y. Okay, it's coming. It's here.
Meaning to knit uh com compilation.
Okay, net.
Oh, this means net, right?
I like Yamikan but it will be better if
they gave readings in Kuny
like that. I think I will have to you go
here and search.
Okay. Uh knit plain braid twist edit
completed poem part of a book. Hi. Can
you hear me?
Am
okay.
Benoet
am.
Thank God
ho
h.
Okay. Uh where was I?
Dano and yeah and
I read this as t that's why I got
confused.
Um
uh she
sign
uh
Um, so yeah, it's basically um
Mary gives uh the Valentine's gift,
which is a sweater, to Teeshi,
and he's really surprised and happy to
receive a a Valentine's gift from Mary
and uh he asked like did you knitted
yourself and Mary is like yes I did I
wonder if it's um
small
or not
uh where
and uh Teshi is like it's it fits
uh it fits and thank and says thank you.
Hi. Uh yeah, this is a translation.
Did you need that? Oh yeah, I forgot one
more. Yeah, I wanted one like this.
Yeah. Yeah, this was important.
Um
what is it? I forgot.
Yeah, I wanted something like this. And
she
made it for Hi. Third one.
Third one. Hi. Next
we have Mary and Hiat.
Oh, wait. It's John. Okay. No, sorry.
It's John and Teshi. Okay. Two friends.
Uh, boi.
No.
Wait, what?
Can you say that? Wait.
No, no, I'm taking it out of context.
Oh, it's in context to the sweater.
Okay, never mind.
Um,
uh,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Cool. Wait.
Wait. What? Wait. Oh my god. What
happened to me? How do I This is Wait.
Uh. Okay. Okay. Wait wait wait wait
wait.
Cool is like this though. Okay. Could Oh
my god, I forgot.
Cool.
Wait.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Hi. Hi. Uh,
okay. So this one would be um Oh my god.
I can't
Oh.
Ah, it was Ro. I forgot. How can I forot
Rohtoan?
Wow. Ch.
Then he got 10 chocolates or something.
It
Wait.
I am a
wait.
Roberto
Santo.
Wait, this is ho, right?
Oh my god, what happened to my uh what?
That is ho. That has to be ho.
Yeah,
I need to read more. Oh my god, this is
bad. D
is bad. I got If I don't practice,
I need to practice again.
Hawai
there there. Right. Wait
there. There there.
Yeah. I there. There. Yeah. Wine there.
Oh, white today. Oh, white today. Oh,
it's white today. Oh, yeah.
Why?
Um,
auto
sun gets
uh
uh sun gets
Y
Oh my god.
Oh my. Okay, let's read this all again.
Okay.
she
rober
Oasan
got Wait.
Oasa like family.
Can't I like look up look it up? I have
to.
Well, this is me.
Can I put it here and search?
Okay. Oh, okay. Then other one
house
here.
Oh yeah. Oh. Oh yeah. Okay. Okay. Oh
yeah. Son.
Oh yeah. Son,
okay, okay, okay, okay. Oh, yeah.
I was like, "Oh, like family owner,
family head or something."
Oh yeah.
White
hand.
get.
Uh uh.
Oh my god. Let me read it.
Why am I reading as
that? Why am I like reading it like
that? That's wrong.
in the sea
distinguish oya from oa
it's 1 hour already
uh that is done
vocabulary
Okusa someone's your or someone's wife.
Um
go go
husband.
Wait
is husband.
Go.
I thought it was a monster though.
Uh, what do you
say?
Wait.
Japanese.
Wait, wait.
Ah,
this
go.
Okay.
Pa partner.
Oh, Jesus.
Uncle, auntie aunt
Jen Rio parents
do
Rio.
Oh. Ah, yeah. Yeah. This one. Oan.
Oh yeah.
And Lord land lady
mean not everyone
mandarin orange. Okay.
Uh, sweatshirt.
Wait, that's not sweatshirt.
sweaters and um to uh to
to
Okay. Uh
shots shots shirt
scarf. Okay.
Oh.
Wait, did I just say good? No. Right.
Okay. No. Hi.
Manga comic book. Um
Ben
cosmetics
rai
Christmas
Valentine day. invite to the yet another
gift giving the
adjective.
Yeah, let's go through this last thing
and I will
after that I'll just read some news
thingy like a few lines of these. Okay.
And then we can wrap up I guess
soon. Okay. Okay.
Then I might stream again later. Okay.
After class, um probably it's going to
be 2 hour long.
Need
me?
Wait. Need you.
Uh, need you.
Uh, wait. I forgot the time. Wait. Go.
Wait. Yeah. Go. Nu.
Wait. Go. Ni. Ni.
Ni.
Go. Wait, wait, wait. How do I say PM?
Goen.
Oh, go
yo.
Yo.
Uh 42 uh
okay goi
y
gou
Uh,
it's not
Yon.
Wait.
Oh my god.
43 and Japanese.
Okay.
So,
this. Okay.
Yeah. I have to add minutes now.
Oh my god.
Um, like
what
Or do you say basics?
Basics in Japanese. Khon.
Yeah.
And this me is going to survive in Japan
next month.
Oh, your boy.
Hi.
stylish
ketchu
to send something.
Uh
something okay
to look good.
Hey uh
to give up
to give
to give me. Yeah.
Uh the key the uh the
wait
the
to be able to do right the wait
to come next to be made. Okay.
Hi
regular
one.
Um
pro prop pro
prop
pro
uh quen
versus Mr.
V.
Uh
like this
suddenly
uh
that's correct. No. Okay.
What should one do?
Counter
small items.
Bound volumes.
Bonds like
bonds
then equi
animals
h book brain oh go that's okay let's do
something um
let's try to make a sentence with this.
Okay, I'll just narrate it vocally.
I'm sure it's going to be 100% wrong.
Bad grammar usage, but I'll try. Okay.
Hi. Uh, okusa. Hi. Let's make a sentence
with that.
Uh,
sentence. No. Wait. What was the
mance
bun? Hi
Wait,
no.
Why do I feel like it's wrong? Mate,
wait. What the? I have an idea.
I have an idea. I have an idea. Times
like this, we use AI.
Uh, okay. Okay.
Uh, times like this, we just use AI, I
guess. All right.
Gemini.
Okay. Hi.
Okay. So, I am trying to I So, wait. So
I will try to make a sentence
using these vocab words.
Do let me know if it's correct
if I if I if I am using the grammar
stuff properly
properly etc.
Hi.
Okay, let's try
us. Yeah, I don't need that. Okay. Hi.
I'm going to type. Okay.
Uh, Japanese keyboard.
He know
the
Korean.
son.
Okuson.
Okus. It's a living being. Okay.
Kino.
Wait, wait, wait. I can do it like this.
Coen.
Coen Park.
No.
Oh,
okusan
mash.
Okusan.
Oh, wait. No, it's a living being.
Uh, August
me.
My god. Is this correct?
Wait. What the uh focus on right. Is
this correct?
I have to put Okay.
Wait.
Okay. Means was visible
could be seen. Hello Chanda. Welcome. Uh
good morning. Uh we are doing Japanese
studies. Uh we were like revising. I
have my exam on Sunday. N4 exam on
Sunday. So yeah, we were like going
through the va v vocabulary stuff and uh
vocabulary stuff and um I'm trying to
make a sentence out of these vocabs so
that way I can get to know right. uh try
to put grammar and everything. Are you
in Japan? Not yet. Next month onwards I
will be in Japan. Currently I'm still in
India.
Next month I I'll be going to Japan for
my language studies. So yeah,
coming back I can understand but
Oh,
yeah.
I could use Oh. Oh, yeah.
JP translator. I know.
I like Japanese lang as a language and
culture wise and everything. So that's
why I'm going there to study language
and do work everything like that.
So thank you for the follow.
Thank you.
Where India are you from? I can't say
that I'm a VTuber. Um you could you
could say I'm from Yeah, I'm from India.
Yeah, somewhere in India I take a guess.
I guess I don't know.
But yeah, I could say in south. Yeah,
I'm from south. You can say I'm not good
at Hindi. So yeah, you're from HYD.
Hydropath,
right? So you're from the north.
That's nice.
Hi. Why changes Coen? I assume Coen was
meant for park. Okay.
Okay. Okusive.
Uh
a far
I
looked at
happened to she me.
Ah, I could have used this
mikashta. So, I am taking a walk in the
park. I saw Teshi's wife sitting in the
park.
Sitting on a bench in a park. How do I
say that? Wait,
how do I say that? I never met someone
who is learning learning uh
Japanese in India.
Yeah, there are a lot of people from
India who are like um who learns Japan
Japanese
cuz many people are into anime and
stuff. No, so they try to learn Japanese
and take JPT exams or NAT exams.
So yeah. So yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. There are I I know a few people
who are from India who are like trying
to study Japanese
etc.
I do watch anime but I don't learn
Japanese.
Could be because they got like that um
motivation or something an urge to learn
a language. Right. they see this cool uh
cultural stuff, all these uh Japanese
media, anime, music, etc. They're like,
I also want to uh I also want to learn
the language, right?
So, they're done. Tell me a dialogue
from anime. I don't know. What do I say?
I don't know. Give me a line. I'll try
to say
oh I know we got ads. All right. So yeah
uh we can also say
um kino
kino
I
So
there
she
Go.
How do you say bench in Japanese?
Uh,
sitting on a bench.
How do I say that?
Uh,
okusa.
Oh my god. Wait, I want to Google
translate this.
Ben Japanese.
Oh, you just Okay.
Okay. Thank you, Ben. Um
Ben
me
wait me uh m M
Oh, thank you for the follow on kick.
Mac the knife. Thank you for the follow
on kick. Hello. Hello. Welcome in. Good
morning.
Uh, you're trying to connect multiple
actions into one longer thought. Okay,
let's refine the grammar.
Wait, wait, wait.
While I was working, walking.
Correction.
Okay.
H
uh while I was walking and then Nagada
is for doing two things at once like
eating while walking. Ah
so that's why
okay
did I write?
Ah my bad. Okay. Uh, okusan.
Oh, okay. Since wife is a person and you
are sporting the object of action, we
use o. O.
Oh, that's a thing. Oh my god.
To see someone in active sitting, we use
the they form plus no.
Oh my god, these grammar stuff
you keep forgetting. But yeah,
hello Kisa. Good morning.
Okay,
the Polish version.
Yesterday while I was walking in the
park, I happened to see Teshi's wife
sitting on a bench. Okay.
The thing is now I can't use basic
Japanese
cuz I'm not N5 level. I'm currently
studying N4 now. So I have to expand a
basic sentence
and make it more
distinctive and I more give it more
explanation. No.
So yeah bye. Oh god
please. I don't want to study anymore.
Yeah. Bye.
Hello Kasa. I hope you're doing well.
Hi
Okay. Say okay
and that is uh
Okusa. Okay.
Uh goen. Okay. Let's try goin. Okay.
Let's make a sentence.
Think think. This is actually good
practice actually. this is a good
practice like I'm not only learning a
vocabulary
uh and um not only I'm learning a
vocabulary the words the vocab I'm also
learning how to use the grammar gram
grammar stuff how do I uh use sentences
in a sentence how do I use it correctly
and stuff that is really nice
so it couldn't eat.
I blame your steady stream for it.
What do you mean? You can't blame it on
me. I'm just studying though.
Uh, okay. Let's make a sentence. Uh,
husband, right?
Uh,
before we saw the example, it was Mary,
right? Teshi and Mary, right?
Yeah. So, let's take Mary as an example.
So,
uh imagine a scenario where
for right now what I'm thinking is
I'm heading back to my apartment.
I noticed
Mary
the wife saying
uh by to her husband who's going to
work. How will I write that in Japanese?
Oh my god. I'm going I'm giving
situational questions.
I
feel like this system is burning us with
study study study. freaking everyone is
steady when we'll we get out of this
loop. Yeah, I know what I feel you
honestly cuz in my case, right,
I've been slacking off last month and
stuff. Uh I slacked off hard. I just
slept around uh in my bed, woke up like
at odd times or wasted time watching
anime or like reading stuff or like um
music, etc. I think I didn't stream last
month, but yeah. Uh, and now I'm like
last minute studying and I'm like I
cannot fail no matter what. I failed
once and o and not just that like um I
have to like do studies
no matter what. I've been actually
thinking of actually uh taking a break
from streaming too because um when I go
to Japan stuff, not only I have to do
Japanese studies, I have to do part-time
along with it and I have to do my
um
the English literature exam stuff, the
back papers I have to clear out from
Japan.
And I'm like broh
so many things I cannot run away from
studying. All these years I tried
running away and then now I'm like uh
um now I'm like um facing the
consequences.
Uh yeah
really sucks but it is what it is now.
We can't run away from it. We have to
face it.
Hi H coming back.
Uh
how do I make this sentence? Hi,
let's think.
Are you
buy
or what?
Okay.
I don't
what?
No, no, no. Uh,
come back.
Mash
kay mash.
So
wait a wait wait wait wait what am I
doing? Next thing uh English sentence
will be what after doing my part-time
job
I am going back to my apartment.
While
going back to my apartment I saw
Mrs. Mary
saying bye to her.
No, wait. Let's change it. I said uh um
I did finish my part-time job and I'm
going back home, right? I can be like um
um
I come back home and I see uh Mary
greeting her husband who came back from
work.
Right. That's a good That's a good
example.
Oh my god.
Now I'm struggling. But in in a way I
have to say all of this vocally, right?
Oh yeah. Bye.
After a few months.
Okay.
Oh, what the
wait accident? No. Wait.
Oh god. No. Japanese face experience
something. I haven't played games. I
can't play games. I actually uninstalled
the games so I can steady give focus
more.
Uh Kyh
in the middle. Wait, how do I think?
I don't want to cheat.
Uh
Ky
Wait, there's a word which is at the tip
of my tongue, but I can't get it out.
Ah,
I know the word.
Kyush.
Um.
Oh my god.
Can I just for this once a while?
a while.
Okay.
Uh, okay. I I I think I got to ban you.
Uh, official gambling. Yeah. You know,
no self-promoting. Hello. Don't
self-promote. I'm gonna
uh
don't self-promote. Wait, that's a 24x7
channel, right?
Uh go uh
uh vary kick.
Yeah. Don't from my guy.
Uh what the
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Don't self-promote.
I will subscribe if you stop study
India. No, don't subscribe. Save your
money.
Save your money. Treat yourself some
biryani or something or like some uh
something nice
cuz you've been working hard. No, treat
yourself something nice like ice cream
or something.
Uh
oh my god. In between. Oh my.
Oh my god.
I
kind
Jen
Don't you get money from Twitch
subscribers? Uh I mean Twitch takes half
of it though, right?
So I I don't like
like uh I'm not dependent on Twitch
money.
So yeah, I don't want to be dependent on
Twitch money. Plus I I barely get
anything from Twitch.
It's once in a while.
So
I mean for YouTube there
and everything
I got to say that to someone's wife.
Okay. Um
medicine.
Uh medicine.
She is greeting her husband. How do I
say that?
raise on G
a G.
Ah,
no.
M go.
How do I say this correctly?
Oh my god.
Um,
you're speaking it, but I'm feeling the
embarrassment. Why?
Wait, do you speak Japanese?
I also
my speaking stuff is I don't practice
Japanese much now. So I don't have
anyone to speak Japanese so I'm bad at
it.
Yeah, speaking and reading those are my
weakness.
Listening is okay.
speak Russian and Italian. Wow, that's
so nice.
Russian, italico.
Shu.
Yes, I agree. You're bad at it. Oh,
yeah. I'm bad at it. Yes, of course I'm
bad at it. I'm bad at my own language,
mother tongue. I'm bad at English. I
only use symbol English, not
um yeah,
not properly articulated English. Yeah,
somewhere else. And I'm learning another
language, Japanese.
Uh
oh. Uh no, no, no, no, no. Okay. Okay.
Okay. I accidentally all uh control Z.
Okay.
Uh
I shouldn't Oh,
greeting. Uh how do I say greeting?
Greeting. Uh,
I'm sorry for cheating while using
Google Translate.
Uh,
great thing. I sat it. You're bad at
something. You shouldn't do it in public
streams. It doesn't matter though.
It doesn't matter though.
See how Wait. Let me just finish this.
uh questions. Oh, I
I s I
s
she mash
mash
mash.
Is this correct? Okay, coming back. If
you're bad at something, you shouldn't
do it on public stream. I mean I did my
I'm bad at singing. I did it publicly.
Uh while being
bad at it on stream I'm at sang. I am
bad at drawing as I drew on stream. I'm
bad at making music. I produced music on
stream
and I'm here learning a language which
I'm bad at while on stream. It doesn't
matter I think. Like see um
in a way I see uh my journey as darkness
is like
uh I had a lot of hobbies and I'm trying
to find myself and what what do you call
it? Um, I know I'm uh jack of all trades
and master of none and I'm bad at
things, but I have the interest to do
something,
learn a skill, right? So, me doing it on
a or like let it be a video or like
publicly online is in a way to showcase
that yeah, I'm trying to do my best and
I'm going to do it. regardless of the
outcome.
Yeah. So then like then I can like
always look back at it like Yeah. during
um
uh during uh
so and so years back I used to learn
Japanese and this was me trying to
uh learn it though I was bad at it and
over time I improved or something. I can
like after like 2 3 years I can if I'm
good at Japanese speaking voice and
everything
um I can go back and like there's like a
memory or some memory lane to look back
right
yeah so I think of it like a journey
though
I mean even on Twitch itself right you
see a lot of
uh smaller streamers who are uh learning
how to draw or like drawing streams,
right? I I do watch a few people who are
who are just just streams just they're
drawing and everything
just learning to draw all those stuff
while like studying or working in the
background. I'll just watch some sh and
like it's nice they're doing their best,
right? So, I can take it like that.
Yeah.
But yeah, condonentwise, uh it's a bit
odd and not that fun, I guess, cuz
people would like to see something
entertaining and fun, right? And that is
there too.
Yeah, that's the thing. That's why I'm
like uh sometimes when I wish to do some
activities,
I'm like uh should I do this stream?
Of course, I can always stream on my old
account or something.
Uh or like a new account or something.
Just no one's going to watch it. I'm
just going to do it or something like
that. Right. It's like some people would
make a YouTube channel and post their
uh process, right? Like day one of me
reading a book, day two of me reading a
book like that.
Okay, you need to add small
there. When you're going to a place
returning home, you use ni or ah
uh the basics I forgot. Grammar usage
either or toki
usually means during continuous duration
since returning is a transition.
Ku toki. Ah. Oh my god.
I could have used to
brain didn't brain much.
Kitchi on the Oh, Kyi on the way home.
Okay, I think I am bad at vocabulary.
Um, I don't know the right words to use.
Um,
quick cultural note. In Japanese, we
rarely say her husband using kare him.
Usually, we just say, "Oh god, I have to
go orin."
Okay.
Wait, did I write it like that?
I did. I have to use Mary again.
Germany knows naturally. Yeah, Germany
is smart. Google Google is smart.
Wow.
Oh,
okay.
Okay. I can't use that. You almost had
it. Just remember the E in shimashta.
Oh, I thought she must stop.
Isachima
when part-time work finished while
returning to the apartment I greeted
Mary's husband.
Hi.
By the way, I'm teasing you. Oh, where
you were? Oh, come. Oh, wait. Did I tell
already that did I mention already that
I'm super dense and bad at understanding
jokes and thesis? all those stuff. So, I
take it seriously.
Wait, did I mention that disclaimer? I
should write it somewhere like in my
about pan or something. So, yeah. I
don't get it when someone's teasing me
or joking or like
something. It happens.
If I wasn't, I would be listening to
ugly words. Oh,
okay. Challenge time. I can see Sarasa
gets over your head.
Sarcasm. What was sarcasm again? Oh my
god.
Mo convey contempt.
Oh, I forgot that's a thing.
Another small one. Yeah, I I don't I'm
not good at this stuff.
Go away. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Oh my god. That's why I'm too gullible.
I think
not. I think I am gullible.
Yeah. It's bad. It's bad.
No.
Yeah, I'm too gullible. Oh my god. Too
much for this world.
Bye.
Okay, let's see. Next to our vocabulary,
you're too innocent. Yeah, I'm too
innocent and that's bad.
I already suffered a lot being too
innocent.
So, yeah.
Oh, it's going to be 12. Okay, we we
went past the two 2our mark. No. Okay.
So, I can expect my teacher to call me
and message me saying that, okay, join
for class right now or something.
Uh,
okay. We can like transition to a
talking section, right? We study for 2
hours.
Don't worry, I'll be stud. Excuse me.
Okay. I Okay.
Hey. Uh,
you've lost it once, you can't get it
ever again. I mean, I lost it actually.
Honestly, I think I lost that thing
public in public sense. I think I lost
it
due to stuff happened to me.
Uh, so I don't know. At this point, I
don't care.
Yeah, at this point I don't care uh if
the uh if uh people still see uh still
view that way.
Uh it is what it is. But uh deep down I
know that yeah uh
yeah deep down I know that I'm not like
that. I people can change all those
stuff, right?
Yeah.
So then it
but yeah some I mean there are people
who think like I'm acting all of this
like bro you haven't seen me I like I
I'm like super shy and silent and I the
same way I am I am I too.
Yeah,
it's hard to like play a character now.
I tried doing that, but it is hard.
So, all I can do is show my real self
how I am.
Okay, today is 10th of March.
So I have 11 12 13 1 2 3 and 4
4 days left for my exam.
13th night I will be going traveling to
that place.
Oh yeah, this would be my last uh train
ride with my family. Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait. Did I tell you guys about the
trip I went with my family? Uh like we
went for a trip.
Yeah,
we went for a trip and it was fun.
Uh visited a lot of places.
Show
uh we're going to I'm going to just
going to be here. We talk for like uh 30
minutes or something.
Uh and we'll wrap it up. Okay.
I didn't. Oh yeah. So apparently I went
to Valagani. I don't know if you know
that place in India.
Um so I went there with my family. We
visited churches stuff.
I think I Yeah, I posted a community. I
did a community post. I I took pictures
of like pigeons actually.
I took pictures of pigeons.
Wait, let me let me find it.
I took pictures of pigeons I found
randomly.
There are like a lot of pigeons.
So we went like to this uh we saw like
this mosque I believe
and on top there one of the um buildings
there were like so many
pigeons. Wait, where is that post? Okay,
I find I found it. Yeah. Yeah, this one.
Hi. Let me show my screen. Um,
yeah. Yeah, this one. I put like the
YouTube sticker.
So, yeah, I was like, so many birds
here. I took that
and then I went to like a um I think
this was inside the church. They like
there was like um sanctuary or
something, a bird sanctuary. There was
like chicken and like doves and stuff.
Birds were here.
And this guy was like this this birdie
did not flinch at all. I was trying to
put my finger inside the metal grid.
It didn't flinch. It was there looking
at it. What is this human doing?
Oh my god. This is nice.
Yeah,
butts are nice.
Oh, boy.
Did I give you guys a story about how um
recently Oh, yeah. This is a recent
event. Okay, I can say this as well. So
my one of my uh okay not one of my so my
mother cat
uh who already gave children like I
think uh she did her
seventh generation kids already and now
the eighth generation kids are coming
apparently. So, I don't know why every
night nowadays
so many sh stray cats are coming to my
house. They're fighting
like they're fighting. They're like
howling, etc. My dog is like barking at
the night because of their fights.
It's It's
crazy though.
Yeah, cats
give birth to children so much now.
Kittens so much, right? Yeah.
And she's pregnant right now. And the
howling stopped.
So the howling stopped.
Meow. Meow. That every night.
Uh
oh yeah the sixth generation cat. No
fifth sixth one died. All of them died
sadly. Uh fifth one is still alive. Um
yeah, he has been No, she has been
really um um like
um always um
uh behind my leg like whenever I walk
out to my backyard, the the the cat door
will be like coming to me and like
pet me, pet me kind of thing.
really nice and cute.
Learn something from a cat. Wait,
I don't want to like I don't think I
should um focus on relationships or
anything right now. I want to just focus
on my life thingy for now. Then I can
worry about it later. Yeah, no worries.
I got so much on my plate already. Like
priorities now,
learning Japanese,
clearing exams, getting a degree and
stuff later so I can do masters.
You should
I'm still young.
I was I'm not old.
Nact.
I'm a healthy person. O, don't say that.
Oh my god,
it's becoming an unsafe stream now.
Oh boy.
Hightech my throat. Let me drink some
water. Okay. Hydration reminder
everyone. Drink some water. Me too.
Hey.
Oh boy.
Okay. Uh, today is like uh Tuesday,
right? Okay. So, tomorrow I'm not sure
if I can stream. I I you know what? I'll
try to stream
cuz again, if I'm streaming, I can only
do steady streams cuz I have to give uh
super attent too much attention to this
right now.
But yeah,
uh in un in other news, uh I recently
made something. Um that's also the
reason why I stream today.
So, uh for my archive website thingy I
was doing recently, right? Um
now, uh kick chat is going to be logged.
He
so I uh made like a recorder. It scans
my chat whenever I'm live. Yeah, both
the 247 channel and the joking joking
channel. Whenever there's a new message,
it scans it. It runs every 6 hoursish.
Uh I I did that. Yeah. So I'm like I I
had still more stuff to do. Then I was
like, "Yeah, study is priority, right?
Exam priority.
I'll
keep those stuff aside. I'll just do
these later.
Not uh these are not important
important, right? Yeah. And also
is coming to Fortnite on 13th or 12th, I
guess. Yeah, 13th. Yeah, 13th.
Man, my Oshi is coming to Fortnite. I
want to buy her, but I'm broke.
Uh,
so he say skin
having a relationship is important. I
had my fair experience of bad relations,
man.
I don't want to go through that again.
No.
No. I'm I'm done.
Oh god. acting up to bite as a man to
bite than any
uh it's more like unrequited I guess uh
or something.
Some came to me I rejected things. It
was an awkward situationship. Yep.
Uh
yeah, I mean at this point my stuff is
already public. Whatever happened
cuz I had to give the whole
Yeah, I don't want to bring this up
again. Yeah, but yeah, it's over.
Uh but
honestly, it's dumb.
Now it's a complicated situation. Uh
kind of
uh cuz again I prioritize my goals
first,
right? like um
like say uh see
I don't want to say this but
but yeah like uh
like it's important to prioritize what
you wish to do and stuff right
uh like knowing that oh you have someone
and you're like
yeah I don't want to worry about my
future I'm going to forget it just kind
of uh be in love or something. That's
dumb. You still have to do your own
stuff, right?
And uh yeah,
I learned it the hard way. Yeah.
You know,
you shouldn't sacrifice yourself for
someone. You shouldn't change yourself
for someone.
should have standards, etc. Don't lower
your lower standards and stuff, etc.
Yeah, bye. Yeah, all those stuff.
Wait, why am I in Apex Legends category
on kick? What?
VTuber. What the?
Okay, change the category. That's weird.
Talk next changed their game to
freaking hot. No, I am I I'm not hot or
anything. I don't take pictures of
myself. I uh
I don't want to say I hate myself, but
I'm trying to
more introvert and everything, but I
should take care of myself more.
So
your mental health matters a lot, right?
And that is important.
Oh, wait. Oh, my stuff. Uh,
what the where is my
There you go. That was off. My bad.
That was off.
Anyway, uh let's uh uh stop talking
about these stuff. Uh we are done for
today. It is uh 2:30.
Wait, two uh 2 hour 30 minutes. Uh we
will wrap it up here. Uh
so uh we did some Japanese um stuff and
that is enough. I'll go back to study. I
have classes, special classes in like 1
hour from now. So I'll go eat and then
eat and then wrap up.
Yeah. Hi. So uh not sure if I'll stream
at night. If I'm streaming at night,
probably I have to re revise kanji.
Uh I'll to revise kanji. So this website
I recommended in the beginning of the
stream. Let me show that again.
Hi. This website it's called kanji kana
it's called. So it's a really good
website. I recommend it. So uh so far I
um
I uh yesterday I uh till 1000 p.m. I
>> I finished this whole line I believe.
Yeah, this one is a bit hard. I still
have to learn this. So yeah, it's 170
kanji. So I know it's too much. There's
more pages. Yep. so much. There's more
pages.
>> Uh all I can do is um
>> uh since this last moment, I can only uh
go through the words,
>> right? The words. So that's what I've
been doing at night. So I'll do that.
And I have the try and for PDF as well,
uh which I will be doing.
Yeah,
>> I'll get some advice from my teacher
today during class what I could do cuz
again I regret um again I'm wasting time
and well slacking off but yeah it's okay
I'll also do an as well not sure but
again it will be steady stream okay
eat me what don't say those Wait,
value yourself. Okay. Hi. Anyhow, so we
will be wrapping it up here. Thank you
all for this for coming by for it was a
short stream. Uh hi.
And probably tomorrow as well if I'm
doing a stream before my afternoon
classes. Uh it will be around this hour.
I'll be ending it. So yeah, once again
do have a a good um Tuesday ahead and
have a good one and do have if you're
from India or yeah if you're from like
uh if it's morning for you have a good
one a good day ahead if it's evening
afternoon have a good lunch etc night
have a good night yeah
hi so yeah
um BLAT.
What is that? Oh, yeah. You learn. You
know Russian, right? Oh, hi. Hi.
Bye-bye. Good night. Wait, not good
night. Have a good one. Take care. Hi.
Hi. Thank you for watching. Have a good
one everyone. This was Jocnex.
I will be redirecting you to my V
channel. Hi.
Currently, it's uh we're playing
Minecraft in my watch channel. So, I'll
be raiding my channel then. So, yeah.
Bye-bye. Have a good one.